essaypro.com 2019-04-10

# Privacy Policy | EssayPro

Below is EssayPro.com’s comprehensive privacy statement. While the fundamental aspects of EssayPro’s privacy statement may not change, we advise all recurrent users to carefully examine the details of our privacy policy from time to time as they are subject to change.

## Gathered User Information

Information gathered about our clients is used only to improve our services and to provide support to our customers. No personal or payment information is given to third parties.

Additionally, our web server only gathers data such as IP address, browser type, times of access, and operating system type for statistical purposes only. Cookies are also sometimes used for the purpose of customizing your webpage’s content on our site.

## Cookies

Essaypro.com website may gather information about your general Internet use by using cookies. Where used, these cookies are downloaded to your computer automatically. A cookie is a text file that is placed on your hard disk by a web page server. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you. Essaypro.com website uses 'cookies' to help you personalize your online experience.

By cookies, we are referring to text files that identify any computer to the server. These only identify the computer but never the specific individual user by name. EssayPro uses cookies to gather information about our web traffic and to understand how we can improve our services in the future. Cookies are an effective measuring system to determine how much time a given user stays on a certain page on our website. Nevertheless, users are always allowed to receive notifications when cookies are used and they may turn off cookies if they desire. However, when cookies are turned off certain personalized aspects of our website may not be available.

You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser settings to decline cookies. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of the EssayPro.com services or websites you visit.

Third party links provided on our website may also use cookies, over which EssayPro.com has no control. Such cookies (if used) would be downloaded once you click on their advertisement banners on our website or visit their sites.

## Optional Information Use

On certain pages of EssayPro.com, you will be requested to give personal information such as name, contact info, or email address. However, any personal information that you provide on our website will never be disclosed to any third parties. We only request this information to facilitate communication between our clients and us while they are trying to submit or retrieve orders. Any demographic details that you give us are only used for our company’s marketing research.

When contacting us via email to provide your feedback, request a service, or more details about our services, your personal information (i.e. your email address) is used to contact you. However, your personal information is never shared, given, or sold to any outside sources or companies, unless you disclose it yourself by communicating via chat with other users.

While you can terminate your account at any time, your information may remain stored in our server archives even after the deletion or termination of your account. However, we will not sell, transfer, or use the information relating to the terminated account of an individual in any way.

The transmission of information via the internet is not completely secure and therefore Essaypro.com cannot guarantee the security of data sent to us electronically. Thus, transmission of such data is therefore entirely at your own risk.

## Future Privacy Policy Amendments

If our privacy policy terms and conditions are modified in the future, we are not obligated to contact you. Continually re-reading our privacy policy from time-to-time is the sole responsibility of the client and not EssayPro.com. It is, therefore, urged and encouraged for all our clients to regularly read our privacy policy for any changes that may affect their experience with our company.

## Website Security

We perform routine security checks and have secure systems in place to ensure that your payment and personal information is always private, protected and only visible to our company. Please DO log out from your accounts if you use any device that can be used by any people other than you, like Internet café or others, to keep your data safe and protected, and avoid any hacking.

Our Links Disclaimer

For all links to other websites posted on our website, we do not explicitly or implicitly endorse their products, content, opinions, services, views, accessibility, policies, or products. If you follow these links to other sites from EssayPro, we are not responsible for that website and you are subject to, but are not limited to, the other website’s written terms, conditions, and privacy policies.

Prohibited Disclosures

Usage of information from both employees and employers related to this privacy policy are for the exclusive use of the commissioner responsible. Information on this website is not open to the public and may not be used in any court of law during any action, legal or otherwise unless the commissioner is responsible for the actions claimed by the other party. A claim of benefits will be determined and made to the affected parties at the commissioner’s discretion. It is also possible to legally pursue parties who abscond on payment.

Do not disclose your personal information or payment data communicating via chat with other users in your profile for security reasons.
